Privacy Policy
==============

INTRODUCTION
------------

SAVE ALL LTD (aka “Gizmo”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and to being transparent about the data we collect about you, how it is used, and with whom it is shared.

This Policy describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing your information through [https://www.gizmo.ai](https://www.gizmo.ai/) (our “Website”) and any associated software, mobile application (“App”), or platforms (together with the Website, and App, the “Service” or “Services”).

Please read this Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our terms, your choice is not to use our Services. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued access of our Website or use of our Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Last Modified Date at the top of this Policy, to ensure that you are viewing the most current version of this Policy.

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
------------------

Gizmo does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 (or applicable age of consent to process personal information in your country) without parental consent, unless permitted by law. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 (or applicable age of consent to process personal information in your country) has provided us with personal information, we will delete it in accordance with applicable law.

THE WHO, WHAT, WHEN, WHERE, AND WHY OF OUR PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We collect several types of information from you and about users of our Services, such as name and contact information when you sign up for our Services or information relating to your studies. We may also collect is information related to how you use our platform, which helps us improve our Services. Please see the table below for more details about our collection and use of your personal information.

### Personal Information Provided by You

You and/or Your Parent/Guardian’s Personal Information

* including email address, and/or phone number, and name, and birthday.

This personal information is collected when:

* registering for an account on our Website or App.
* you communicate with us or other users on our Website or App.
* required by law, we will request the contact information of your parent or guardian.

This personal information is collected to:

* identify you and to address your inquiries.
* send you feedback requests or surveys, and updates about our product and services (e.g., updates about new features, notifications of bugs, and guides on how to use the product.) \*You can opt-out at any time by unsubscribing from the emails you receive.

User-Generated Data

* including text-inputs, messages, study materials, photos, videos, or other data shared while using our AI features.
* You input this information when uploading study materials to our Website or App.

This personal information is collected to:

* provide you with our Services; including to create quizzes, and other content that helps you study and learn.

Non-Identifying Information

* including zip codes, demographic data, time zone, publicly available data, and general information regarding your use of the Service.
* This information is collected automatically.

This personal information is collected to:

* provide you with our Services.
* improve our Services.

Payment Information

* including credit card, billing address, and other financial information necessary to purchase or otherwise use our Services.
* This information is collected if you purchase a subscription using our Website or App.

This personal information is collected to:

* deliver, provide, and process payment for the subscription you requested.

User Contributions

* This is any information you choose to share with other Gizmo users.
* This information is collected when you interact with parts of our Website, such as the ability to post public comments or share information with other users.

This personal information is collected to:

* provide you with Our services.

When you provide us with information in connection with a particular activity or otherwise sign up for or order our products and Services or provide your contact information to us, including your email address or telephone number in connection with that activity, product or service, you agree that such action constitutes a purchase or inquiry establishing a business relationship with us. You expressly consent to receiving communications from Gizmo through the information you provided to us. For more information on how to access and control your communication preferences, please see YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION, below.  
  
Please note that along with the reasons listed above, may also use the information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, for the following reasons:

* To tailor content we display to you and any offer we may present to you, both on the Service and via email.
* To comply with legal requirements and assist law enforcement.
* To investigate fraud and stop any activity, we may consider to be illegal, fraudulent, unethical or a legally actionable activity, and to protect the property rights of Gizmo.
* To protect the safety of Gizmo users.
* For the purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information, and
* As otherwise permitted with your consent.

### Information Collected Automatically

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, We and our third-party service providers, including analytics, may automatically collect certain information from you whenever you access or interact with the Service.

* Usage Information. Details of your visits to our Website, including which links you clicked on, content response times, location data, logs, and other similar communication data and statistics about your interactions.
* Device Information. Information about your computer and internet connection, including your Internet Protocol address, operating system, and browser type.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, analytics, and site functionality.  

### Cookies and Other Automatic Data Collection Technologies

Gizmo and its partners use cookies or similar technologies, which store certain information on your computer and allows us to, among other things, analyze trends, administer the Website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The technology used to collect information automatically from Gizmo Users may include the following:  

* Cookies: Like many websites, we and our and service providers use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use both persistent cookies that remain on your computer or similar device (e.g., to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service) and session ID cookies, which expire at the end of your browser session (e.g., to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how Users interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage, and web traffic routing on the Service). You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functionality of the Service.
* Web Beacons: We and our service providers may also employ software technology known as “web beacons” and/or “tracking tags” to help us keep track of what content on our Service is effective and to serve relevant advertising to you. Web beacons are small graphics with a unique identifier that may be invisible to you, and which are used to track the online activity of Internet users. Web beacons are embedded in the web pages you review or email messages you receive. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to our Service, to monitor how Gizmo Users navigate the Service, to count how many emails that were sent were actually opened, or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.
* Embedded Scripts: We and our operational partners, affiliates, analytics, and service providers may also employ software technology known as an Embedded Script. An Embedded Script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Service, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer or other device and is deactivated or deleted when you disconnect from the Service.

### Information Received from Third Parties

We also may receive information about you from third parties. For example, we and our partners, affiliates and service providers may use a variety of other technologies (such as tags) that collect statistical data relating to your Website activity for security and fraud detection purposes.  
  
You may choose to register to join Gizmo by logging into your account with a third-party via our Service (e.g., Google, Apple and other third-party services that let you sign in using your existing credentials with those services). Note that the information we collect from and through these third parties may depend on the privacy settings you have set with those third-parties and the permissions you grant to us in connection with linking your account with Gizmo.  

### Do Not Track Signal

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. We do not honor browser requests not to be tracked online (known as “Do Not Track”), but our cookie policy below describes how you can opt out of receiving cookies.  

HOW WE DISCLOSE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
------------------------------------------

We don't share any personally identifying information publicly or with third parties, except when necessary to provide you with our services or if required by law. The following explains the reasons necessary to provide you with our services.

* With Parents and Guardians: A parent or guardian may view certain information collected from their child(ren) through the Services and may request information about the information we have collected from their child(ren) by contacting us at the address set forth below.
* With Our Service Providers: We employ third party companies and individuals to provide Services on our behalf, to perform Service-related operations (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, fraud detection and improvement of Gizmo’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information in order to perform these tasks on our behalf.

* When you use our AI enabled features we will disclose user-generated data with our AI service provider for the purpose of performing Service-related operations (e.g., to generate responses, other requested outputs, and for improving AI functionality.)
* Additionally, app stores, such as App Store or Google Play, host our App and process any in-App purchases that you may make, or subscriptions you sign up for. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information in order to perform these tasks on our behalf.

* For Corporate Transactions: While very unlikely, Gizmo may share information, including Personal Information, with any current or future subsidiaries or affiliates, for business and operational purposes. We may sell, transfer, or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets (including, in each case, as part of the due-diligence process with any potential acquiring entity) or in the event of bankruptcy.
* If Required by Law: Gizmo will share information with government agencies as required by law in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements and, including without limitation, in connection with reporting earnings. We will disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials, in our sole discretion, if the disclosure is necessary to (a) protect the property and rights of Gizmo or a third party, (b) protect the safety of the public or any person, or (c) prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or pose a risk of being, illegal, fraudulent, unethical or legally actionable activity. We may also use Device Identifiers to identify Gizmo Users and may do so in cooperation with third parties at our discretion.

YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION
--------------------------------------------------

You have several ways to exercise control over your information:

* Account Settings: Registered Gizmo users may update their choices regarding the types of communications you receive from us through your online Account settings.
* E-Mail: You also may opt-out of receiving marketing emails from us by following the opt-out instructions provided in those emails. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of the Service (for example, administrative and service announcements) via email and other means and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you opt-out from receiving marketing communications.

### California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights

We do not sell personal information of California consumers, have not sold personal information of California consumers in the preceding 12 months, and do not have actual knowledge that we sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age.  
  
If you are a California resident, the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides you with additional privacy rights with respect to our collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information, including:

* The right to know what Personal information we have collected and how we have used and disclosed that Personal Information in the 12-month period preceding your request.

* Please see the above section within this Policy titled THE WHO, WHAT, WHEN, WHERE, AND WHY OF OUR PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, to see the categories of Personal Information we have collected about you and how we use that information.
* Please see the above sections within this Policy titled HOW WE DISCLOSE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION, to see applicable disclosures of your Personal Information.

* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information.
* The right to opt-out of the sale of their personal information.

* As stated above, we do not sell your Personal Information. Therefore, we do not provide an opt-out for the sale of Personal Information.

* The right to be free from discrimination related to the exercise of any of your privacy rights.

For more information on how to exercise your rights, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://saveall.ai/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please note that we may require you to verify your credentials, by matching your e-mail address, and other Personal Information to the information in our systems, before we can fulfill your request. If you authorize another person to act as your agent to submit requests on your behalf, then unless you provide the agent with power of attorney under the California Probate Code, we will ask the agent to provide us the written and signed authorization that you provided to the agent, we will confirm with you that you did provide the authorization, and we will verify your identity.  

INTERNATIONAL JURISDICTIONS
---------------------------

Our Services are hosted and offered in the United States of America (US), and are subject to US federal, state, and local law. If you are accessing the Services from another country, please be advised that you may be transferring your personal information to us in the US, and you consent to that transfer, processing, and storage of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Notice. You also agree to abide by the applicable laws of applicable US federal, state, and local laws concerning your use of the Services and your agreements with us. Any persons accessing our Services from any jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing the use of the Internet, including the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information, different from those of the jurisdictions mentioned above may only use the Services in a manner lawful in their jurisdiction. If your use of the Services would be unlawful in your jurisdiction, you may not use our Services.  

SECURITY
--------

We use physical, technical, and organizational measures designed to protect your information against unauthorized access, theft and loss. We restrict access to your personal information to those employees who need to know that information to service your account or perform their job functions.  
  
Although we take precautions intended to help protect information that we process, no system or electronic data transmission is completely secure. Any transmission of your personal data is at your own risk, and we expect that you will use appropriate security measures to protect your personal information.  
  
You are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and the information in your account. We may suspend your use of all or part of the Services without notice if we suspect or detect any breach of security. You understand and agree that we may deliver electronic notifications about breaches of security to the email address on record on your account.  

LINKS TO OTHER SITES
--------------------

Users also have the ability to connect with us through social media platforms such as Discord. We may, depending on your privacy settings, receive some information from your social media account, and what we collect depends on your privacy settings with that social networking service.  
  
Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies. Additionally, be aware that to use Discord services, you must be 13 years of age or older. For more information, please see Discord’s Terms of Service.  

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
----------------------

Gizmo may update this Privacy Policy at any time and any changes will be effective upon posting. In the event that there are material changes to the way we treat your Personal Information, we will update the Last Modified date at the top of this Policy upon becoming effective. We may also notify you by email, in our discretion.  

HOW TO CONTACT GIZMO
--------------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://saveall.ai/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
